export default [
    {
        question: "drink",
        answer: "boire, bois, bois, boit, buvons, buvez, boivent"
    },
    {
        question: "say",
        answer: "dire, dis, dis, dit, disons, dites, disent"
    },
    {
        question: "laugh",
        answer: "rire, ris, ris, rit, rions, riez, rient"
    },
    {
        question: "smile",
        answer: "sourrie, souris, souris, sourit, sourions, souriez, sourient"
    },
    {
        question: "know",
        answer: "connaître, connais, connais, connaît, connaissons, connaissez, connaissent"
    },
    {
        question: "remember",
        answer: "reconnaître, reconnais, reconnais, reconnaît, reconnaissons, reconnaissez, reconnaissent",
        highlight: "I talks",
    },
    {
        question: "put",
        answer: "mettre, mets, mets, met, mettons, mettez, mettent",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "hear",
        answer: "entendre, entends, entends, entend, entendons, entendez, entendent",
        highlight: "She talks",
    },
    {
        question: "climb down",
        answer: "descendre, descends, descends, descend, descendons, descendez, descendent",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "wait",
        answer: "attendre, attends, attends, attend, attendons, attendez, attendent",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "lose",
        answer: "perdre, perds, perds, perd, perdons, perdez, perdent",
        highlight: "You talks",
    }
]